totobay.com 2009-06-18

# Privacy Policy

|  |  | About Totobay.com  
---|---  
| How to Order  
| Payment Methods  
| Shipping Method  
| Warranty Terms  
| Exchange Policy  
| Return and Refund Policy  
| Order Cancellation  
| Custom Rights  
| Out of Stock Items  
| Frequent Asked Questions  
| Frequence List  
| Drop Shipping Service  
| Bluk Purchase  
| Safe and secure purchase  
| Terms and Conditions  
| Privacy Policy  
| Links  
|  | **Privacy Policy**  
---  
  
  * Your privacy is important to us. We believe that by respecting your privacy we will earn the opportunity to build a lasting relationship with your business, your clients and your staff. Any information you provide to us will only be used for the purpose for which it was submitted. We collect your information primarily for proof, contact and billing purposes. Under no circumstances will your information be shared with, or sold to, or disclosed to any third party, except where required by law.
  * This Privacy Policy applies only to information gathered in connection with Totobay.com's consumer credit card accounts used for transactions at Totobay.com and applications for those accounts.
  * In order to enhance our ability to provide you with the best services, opportunities, and choices possible, we collect, use, and share certain information about you. This policy explains what information we collect, with whom we share it with. The practices described in this policy are applicable to current and former customers and consumers who do business with us. The policy also explains how we protect the security and confidentiality of our customer information.

| Information we collect and sources of information.  
---  
  
  * We may collect information about some of your personal details and documents, (such as, address, copy of credit card statements, identification, etc) all to help us process the order in which you've made, and for us to assure and prove that you are the person paying for the products.

Information we share with service providers or joint marketers.  
---  
  
  * We may disclose some of the information we collect, to companies that perform services on our behalf, including those who assist us in selling, billing, shipping and responding to customer inquiries. We may provide that information to others who perform marketing services for us and to financial institutions with whom we jointly offer financial products or services, subject to any requirements and restrictions of applicable state law.

Security and confidentiality of your information.  
---  
  
  * We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know in order to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state law standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
